Hello hello everyone I had put a question on Twitter today
what is going on in the market
everyone gave their answer but I
think Reliance is doing well this
first video of yours also has news of Reliance
and the second video of Mitti's NSS
will also have news of Reliance only and only
see in today's video we will talk about
this fiber special after that
a big news of ICICI Lombard and
thirdly Adani and
Tata's name is not there in running private trains so
what will be the effect on IRCTC, what can IRCTC say can
stop it, everyone wants to
know so I welcome Purva your Africa
YouTube channel because
people must subscribe to the channel
tap the bell icon and the good news is everyday
on Telegram now they give life level
through which you can earn money whether it is Britain or
not even today benefits have been given so if you are
not connected to Mishra and Twitter then
join today in which the way in which
I have given it is in front of you that
after making a splash in the platform
now Mukesh Ambani is going to make his mark
under the fiber decision
why did the authority come for 10 minutes these rallies  is
talking to and
about an investment of 210 crores and this
investment company's fiber optic bent,
this is the anti-billion dollar fun race,
they have done this by distracting the platform
and now following them is Fiber Left
which holds Jio Digital Fiber Private Limited
and Kapar Investment can
invest 1.5 to 2 billion dollars in Reliance Power. Reliance has hired Citigroup Global
Markets, Poems & Company and
ICICI Securities Limited as
investment
bankers for this deal but the
problem here is that this is not official news, this is
news from the source because when we
emailed the people who were hired, we
refused to give any kind of reply,
hence this is not official news yet, it is
found more, the life is
looted, so their network is 150
km network of fiber optic cable
in India and their expansion plan is of
1.1 million kilometers, so there is a birthday
and you will talk about it and diesel, but
if this happens then it will definitely be a big step
in Jio Fiber where their  The costing
burden will further reduce and we will take it forward better
and there will be better competition in a better market. The
second big news is
related to ICICI Lombard, in which
ICSE Ombudsman and Indian General,
Xtra General, the interesting thing is coming out,
both the insurance companies, the dip of which is being talked about, the
valuation of Bharti AXA General is
said to be Rs 2628 crore and the
maturity share of Bharti Enterprises in Indian education and Xtra is a
French insurance company which
works with joint venture in India and after this bill, a
little
peace will come out and it also
wants to exit, now this approval will
not be possible until the regular approval is received,
but till now this is not official news, it is a
news of thought and we will know very well, as far as
ICC looting is concerned,
this is one of these general insurance companies listed in the Indian stock market and its
share has set gate points in the market
and if I also tell you about such stocks, then the
demand for such people is very good support, you can
get it in the fall at any time.  So you
can also take investment like this, which power
is this juice, now let's move towards such news, that is a
very important news, till now there was a
lot of heat in the market, so there was
repeated news about running private trains
that Tata and Dhani can take up trains,
but
in the current update, only Tata did not stop in the race, the news is
what IRCTC wants to do, everything will go, so
as you know, there, in order to
increase private agencies on coordination, for the
participation of private companies,
privatization has been promoted so that passengers can get the best flight and this will
bring investment in the railways, so as
you know that a few days ago, to
run 151 private trains on 80 pair routes, private companies
only
solicited requests, individual companies were interested that on
20th July, the railways called the interested
companies for a pre-bid conference, in which
sixteen
companies participated and from the 16th,
11 companies participated in the pre-bid, this is the
IRCTC chief, this IRCTC  The
main ones are GSM, apart from this, all of you groups,
Mumbai, Air India, the Rice Dal, my
group, your absorbed Strike Power Bharat
Pooja and Baby Infrastructure are included. Now,
look, the thing to note here is that the
names of Tata and Ambani are not there right now,
this does not mean that they cannot come in the future,
I will tell you about that. Secondly, the
way IRCTC's
name is there in this, first of all, you need to understand IRCTC.
If IRCTC runs more trains, then
when there is so much craze for IRCTC on so many trains,
some Amits will
get the authority to run more trains, then the regulation of their craze will
increase further. The
net profit mark of the share will
increase further, so definitely IRCTC will
become another excellent stop. Apart from this,
whatever name is in the list of electricity bills will
come on withdrawal. Remember, I am
not talking about investment right now, they will
come on the radar, so this is the
stop which we need to pay attention to. If
IRCTC trains run, then the shareholders of IRCTC will
definitely benefit. Now,
according to the Railways, those who have complained about running private trains
can buy or lease the trains of their choice.  So
time will tell who gets on the list and
who buys it. Now the companies have also
asked some questions to the Railway Ministry, so the Railway
Ministry has taken the time of 31 July 2020
and they say that we will give
you the complete returns within a few questions by 31 July 2019.
Now the
second meeting is going to be held on 12th August and in the second meeting,
Aditya will decide that
when there is a mix in this meeting, then it is like that right now
Adani and Adani Group are trying to
increase ridership. Adani Group and
Tata have not participated yet but there are still
opportunities for them and for
running the friend below, you can like there till September, so it remains to be
seen
whether their name comes up in the date till 8 September
or not and it is expected that an
investment of 30 thousand crores will
come in the Railways, due to which employment will increase and
income will also increase. Right now the question is that liquid private
Renu, this thing is coming up again and again, from when will it run,
so it will run like from the screen of March 2012 to
March 2305  There is talk of facilities, there is
talk of getting flight like facilities,
now we have to see in what way we can get it,
as far as IRCTC is concerned,
ICTC is currently running three trains, Kabhi
Mahakal on Banaras Indore,
Billi also on Lucknow, Tejas and on Ahmedabad-Mumbai, let us see
how Gift Trend
and run
Snapdeal, news is very important, when
we treat and invest, then we get
the idea that if we get official confirmation in tomorrow's date then
it is very good
and if we are not able to come in the state tomorrow then
also trading should not be done in bad strategy,
okay, in this way this top is very
useful for us, Newscorp, if you like it then please
like, comment and share and what do you
think, Tata will come to run the train,
definitely tell us.